# **Carl Sachs**

### Full-Stack Developer

In December of 2019, I decided to jump into the growing tech industry, and joined Lambda School for Full-Stack Web Development. I am a motivated and hard-working individual with a knack for juggling projects in a timely and efficient manner. I pick up on concepts quickly, and love to expand my knowledge learning by experience. I am open to both remote and on-site opportunities, and would love to focus in React.js.

### Contact

#### **Address**

Detroit, MI, 48225

#### **Phone**

(313) 330-7308

#### E-mail

sachscarl@gmail.com

#### **WWW**

carlsachs.com

### **Twitter**

twitter.com/CarltonSachs

#### LinkedIn

in/carl-sachs/

### **Skills**

React	
CSS	
HTML5	
Node.js	
Bootstrap	
React Native	
Javascript	

### Education

### 2019-07 -Current

### Lambda School Endorsement, Full-Stack Web Development: Full-Stack Development

Lambda School - Remote

I took Lambda's Full-Stack Web Development course, completed on:

Sep 1st, 2020.

#### Skills:

- React
- Node
- HTML
- CSS
- Knex
- Python
- Javascript
- Team Collaboration
- And more.

### 2017-08 -2019-03

### **Business Finance**

Wayne State University - Detroit

Coursework in Entrepreneurship, Finance, and Business Admin.

• Avg. 3.6 GPA

## **Projects**

Find my Github Profile Here:

Web
Development

TailwindCSS

Publish NPM
Libraries

Expo

React-Native

StyledComponents

Python

https://github.com/carlsachs

#### Find my Projects here:

https://carlsachs.com/projects

### **Work History**

### 2020-09 - Student

#### Current

Lambda X, Remote

- I am currently looking for opportunities and working with Lambda X
- Planned, prepared and participated in weekly meetings and events
- Reported back to instructor and management to receive day-to-day tasks and responsibilities

### 2018-01 -2019-06

### Bartender/Server

Andiamo Detroit Riverfront, Detroit, Michigan

- Learned how to interact with all types of business clientele who frequented the GM Ren Center.
- Collaborated with kitchen team to support order preparation, manage efficient deliveries and minimize customer service issues by verifying meals
- Upsold high-profit items such as appetizers and mixed drinks to increase sales and profits
- Worked with POS system to place orders, manage bills and handle complimentary items
- Enhanced operational efficiency by using slow periods to restock supplies

### 2016-12 - Server

#### 2017-05

Coach Insignia, Detroit, Michigan

- Created a high-end experience for clientele.
- We once spent 3 hours setting and resetting a single table for when Mercedes hosted their Around-the-World party
- My main takeaway was that the small details are what matter most.
- Upsold high-profit items such as appetizers and

mixed drinks to increase sales and profits

 Created orders, documented special requests and followed up with kitchen personnel to foster top-quality service